Willowbrook Review Panel; Records apap127
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- New York Civil Liberties Union Files, 1973-1987; 14; 5 cubic ft.
  - Chronological Records Index, 1979 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 9)
  - Chronological Records Index, Second Copy with Notations, 1979 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 10)
  - US Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit (No. 78 -- 6072), 1979 March 01 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 11)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Community Placement Recommendation, 1979 December-1980 April (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 12)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Flower Fifth Avenue Hospital/Request for Proposal, 1979 March (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 13)
  - Review Panel -- Reduction of Members, ca. 1980 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 14)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Consent Judgment -- Modification, 1980 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 15)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Motion for Contempt, 1980 April 09-1980 April 10 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 16)
  - Addendum to the January 31, 1980 Operation Plan for Placements (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 17)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Attorneys' Fees, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 18)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Attorneys' Fees, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 19)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Attorneys' Fees, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 20)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Attorneys' Fees, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 21)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Attorneys' Fees, 1980-1981 (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 1)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (US Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit Nos. 80 -- 7289, 80 -- 7295): Appeal of April 10, 1980 District Court Decision, June 4 (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 2)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Flower Hospital Compliance Report, 1981 (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 3)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Motion for Contempt, 1987 (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 4)
  - Community Placement Plans, 1981 (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 5)
  - Community Placement Plans, 1981 (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 6)
  - Community Placement, Flower Hospital Placement Plan, 1981 (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 7)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Staffing Compliance Report, 1981 March (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 8)
  - August 22, 1979 Formal Recommendations: 90-Day Progress Report, 1981 (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 9)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Motion to Modify Sections of the Consent Judgment and to Vacate the Three Bed/Six Bed Order, 1981 May (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 10)
  - NYSARC and Parisi v. Carey (No. 72 -- C -- 356/357): Motion to Modify Sections of the Consent Judgment and to Vacate the Three Bed/Six Bed Order, 1981 May (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 11)
  - Compliance Report, Staten Island Developmental Center, 1981 (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 13)
  - Report to the Court, January 1, 1977 to June 30, 1977, 1977 June (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 1)
  - Compliance Report, Willowbrook Related Facilities, 1977 September (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 2)
  - Joint Audit by the Willowbrook Review Panel and the Technical Assistance Unit, 1977 July; 1977 September 28 (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 3)
  - Report to the Court, July 1, 1977 to December 31, 1977, 1977 December (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 4)
  - Staffing Supplement to Compliance Report, Willowbrook Related Facilities, 1978 January (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 5)
  - Compliance Report, United Cerebral Palsy at Willowbrook, United Cerebral Palsy at Nina Eaton Center, 1978 January (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 6)
  - Community Placement Audit, 1977 May-1977 October; 1978 February (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 7)
  - Compliance Report, United Cerebral Palsy at Willowbrook, 1978 April (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 8)
  - Report to the Court, January 1, 1978 to June 30, 1978, 1978 June (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 9)
  - Compliance Report: Willowbrook Development Center, 1978 February; 1978 June (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 10)
  - Community Placement Audit, 1977 November-1978 April; 1978 June (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 11)
  - Operational Audit, 1978 April; 1978 July (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 12)
  - Compliance Report, Willowbrook Related Facilities, 1978 September (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 13)
  - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, Karl Warner Center, Nina Eaten Center, 1978 November (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 14)
  - New York City/Long Island County Service Group's Plan for Placements, 1978 December 01 (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 15)
  - Report to the Court, July 1, 1978 to December 31, 1978, 1978 December (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 16)
  - Mental Retardation Institute (MRI), Flower Fifth Avenue Hospital, 1978 October (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 17)
  - Community Placement Audit, 1978 May-1978 November; 1979 February (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 18)
  - Staten Island Developmental Center Compliance Report, 1979 February (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 19)
  - Staffing Audit Compliance Report: Staten Island Developmental Center (Willowbrook) and the Willowbrook Related Facilities, 1979 February (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 20)
  - Report to the Court, January 1, 1979 to June 30, 1979, 1979 June (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 21)
  - Compliance Report, Willowbrook Related Facilities, 1979 September (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 22)
  - Mental Retardation Institute (MRI), Flower Fifth Avenue Hospital, 1979 October; 1980 January (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 23)
  - Operation Audit, 1979 June-1979 August; 1980 January (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 24)
  - Compliance Report, United Cerebral Palsy Nina Center and United Cerebral Palsy Karl Warner Center, 1979 November; 1980 January (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 25)
  - Community Placement Audit, 1979 May-1979 November; 1980 February (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 26)
  - Report to the Court, July 1, 1979-December 31, 1979, 1980 February (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 27)
  - Staffing Audit Compliance Report, Staten Island Developmental Center and the Willowbrook Related Facilities, 1980 February (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 28)
  - Compliance Report, Staten Island Developmental Center, 1980 March (Box 5 (14-New York Civil Liberties Union ), Folder 29)